[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
Okay.
好
So I have a question for you guys which is, how would you maximize recall?
我想问大家一个问题 如何使得召回率最大?
Remember recall.
还记得召回率吧
We just look at the magenta squares.
刚才我们看的那些洋红色方框
We look at the liked items.
也就是我们喜欢的物品
And we measure how many of my liked items were actually retrieved or
召回率就是我们用来度量有多少我们喜欢的物品 在实际中被检索到或者
actually recommended to me.
确实被推荐给我了
Well, as the title answers, there's a very easy way to maximize recall.
正如标题所回答的 要使召回率最大化有一种非常简单的方法
Just recommend everything.
就是推荐所有的物品
If you recommend everything,
只要推荐了所有的物品
you're guaranteed to recommend the products that I like.
就能保证把我喜欢的产品推荐给我
So in this case what would recall be?
这时候召回率是多少呢?
It would just be 1, because all 5 of the products I liked were recommended.
是1 因为我喜欢的5个产品都被推荐给我了
So this is because there are 5 out of 5 products recommended.
因为5个产品中的5个都被推荐给我了
But what's the resulting precision of doing this?
但是这样做的话精度结果会如何呢?
Well, it can actually be arbitrarily small.
实际上精度会很小
Because if you have tons and tons and tons of products out there, and
因为如果你有很多很多很多的产品
if I like only a very, very small number of them,
并且我只喜欢其中非常小的一部分
then if you recommend everything, I'm gonna have very small precision.
这时如果你把所有东西都推荐给我的话 我会得到很小的精度
So let's just say this is small and maybe very small.
我们只是说精度小 而且可能非常小
So that's not really a great strategy.
所以 这确实不是个好策略
On the other hand, what would be the optimal recommender?
那么 最优的推荐该是什么样的呢?
What's the best recommender you can imagine?
你能想到的最好的推荐是什么?
Well, the best recommender is one that recommends all
最好的推荐是推荐的所有产品 都是我喜欢的并且
the products I like but only the products I like.
只有我喜欢的
So everything that was not liked was never shown by the recommender.
所以我不喜欢的东西都不会出现在推荐中
So that would be great.
这样很棒
No wasted effort,
不做无用功
capture everything I like, gonna make lots of money with this recommender system.
得到我想要的所有物品 这样的推荐系统能赚很多钱
What's the precision and recall?
这时的精度和召回率是多少呢?
Both are 1 in this case.
都是1
And you can go through and
你可以用之前幻灯片中的公式来
verify that using the equations from the previous slides.
检查核实一下
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community